{
    "subject": "resource/Horam",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/United_Kingdom",
    "human_readable": "Horam is from United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8653960824012756,
            "question": "Is Horam British?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6372659802436829,
            "question": "Where is Horam from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5572304725646973,
            "question": "What country is Horam associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5242531895637512,
            "question": "Is Horam from Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5001985430717468,
            "question": "To which nation does Horam belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.459468275308609,
            "question": "What is Horam's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44813287258148193,
            "question": "Horam's origin is in which part of the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41121408343315125,
            "question": "Where was Horam born or raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37727248668670654,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Horam's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.342601478099823,
            "question": "What is Horam's country of citizenship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Horam is from United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8756_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Horam's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8756_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Horam born or raised?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8756_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Horam's origin is in which part of the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8756_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8756_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8756_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8756_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8756_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8756_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8756_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8756_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8756_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8756_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8756_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Horam is located in the United Kingdom. The context clearly mentions Horam as a village situated in East Sussex, England, United Kingdom, which confirms its location within the UK."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}